在站台并肩，是时候改变
Together at the station, time to make the change.
你的裙摆飞扬
君のスカートが広がる
来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧
Get it on, get it on, get it on, get it on
因为不会就此结束
Cause it doesn't have to end
我只想做从未见过的自己
I only wanna be the me I've never seen
宝贝，听风起舞吧
Baby風を聞いて舞い上がれ
来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧
Get it on, get it on, get it on, get it on
因为不会就此结束
Cause it doesn't have to end
带我去天堂
Take me to heaven
啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
La la la, la la la la la la la
啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦
La la la, la la la la la la
当我们翱翔，一次又一次
When we fly and over and over
我知道我能成为我的能量
I know I can be my energy
啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
La la la, la la la la la la la
啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦
La la la, la la la la la la
让我一次又一次翱翔
Got me flying over and over
仿佛能释放我的能量
Seems to be a free my energy
啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
La la la, la la la la la la la
啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦
La la la, la la la la la la
让我一次又一次翱翔
Got me flying over and over
火箭飞驰，释放我的能量
Flying rocket free my energy